How have you learned to vet?
What are the processes and criteria that you use?
I first learned do not hire in a state of desperation.
Sis, you will hire the wrong person.
Man.
I spent 15 years hiring in a state of desperation.
And every time.
Every time.
It's the wrong person.
And then you're stuck.
And unraveling is way harder and more time conducive and expensive
than taking the time to find the right person.
But sometimes you don't have the time.
No, and that's the thing.
Sometimes you don't have the time.
So we were just talking about this because we were about to hire somebody.
And we're like, but it's about to be the down season.
It's about to be Thanksgiving.
I'm not going to have enough work.
And I'm thinking, telling Melissa, like, we actually need the best time.
Let's ramp you up instead of throwing you in where we got shoots and podcasts.
Lesson I learned.
Yeah.
Let's do this while we're going.
Of course, it's a cyclical business.
So you're going to get some weeks or months where it's like, oh, there's less work.
You're going to make up for it when there's more work.